Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Gorgeous Dream= (Adapted from the novel "The Charming Evil Consort.")
=حلم رائع= (مقتبس من رواية "الزوجة الشريرة الساحرة").
=Episode 5=
=الحلقة 5=
Lan Mengyan.
لان منجيان.
What have you done to me?
ماذا فعلت بي؟
Let me out.
دعني اخرج.
And you, Zhu.
وأنت يا تشو.
If this is how you treat me,
إذا كانت هذه هي الطريقة التي تعاملني بها،
my sister,
أختي
my sister will never spare you.
أختي لن تتخلى عنك أبدًا.
If you want to kill me,
إذا كنت تريد قتلي،
it will not be that easy.
لن يكون الأمر سهلا.
Let me out.
دعني اخرج.
Do not be anxious.
لا تقلق.
Your retribution is still ahead.
إن جزاءك لا يزال في المستقبل.
You…
أنت…
What did you make me drink?
ماذا جعلتني أشرب؟
If you disobey, you will not live to see tomorrow.
إذا عصيت فلن ترى الغد.
(Liu Residence)
(مسكن ليو)
It was Xie Ruilan.
لقد كان شيه رويلان.
Xie Ruilan forced me to kill Steward Lou.
أجبرني شي رويلان على قتل ستيوارد لو.
Go quickly.
اذهب بسرعة.
It was Xie Ruilan.
لقد كان شيه رويلان.
Xie Ruilan forced me to kill Steward Lou.
أجبرني شي رويلان على قتل ستيوارد لو.
She bribed the madam.
لقد رشوت السيدة.
She framed Huan Xi.
لقد أحاطت بهوان شي.
All those filthy dealings of the Liu family
كل تلك المعاملات القذرة لعائلة ليو
are in her hands.
هي في يديها.
(The Xie family's year of Wushen ledgers) It was Xie Ruilan.
(سنة دفاتر عائلة شيه ووشن) كان شيه رويلان.
Xie Ruilan forced me to kill Steward Lou.
أجبرني شي رويلان على قتل ستيوارد لو.
She bribed the madam.
لقد رشوت السيدة.
She framed Huan Xi.
لقد أحاطت بهوان شي.
It was Xie Ruilan.
لقد كان شيه رويلان.
Sister.
أخت.
Brother-in-law.
شقيق الزوج.
Father.
أب.
Xie Yaozu kept secret ledgers.
احتفظ Xie Yaozu بدفاتر سرية.
He embezzled the Liu family's assets.
قام باختلاس أصول عائلة ليو.
He even abused decent young women.
حتى أنه اعتدى على الفتيات الشابات المحترمات.
He sullied the Liu family's name.
لقد لطخ اسم عائلة ليو.
Steward Lou's death and Huan Xi's injustice,
موت ستيوارد لو وظلم هوان شي،
all of it was his doing.
كان كل ذلك من صنع يديه.
I ask Father to investigate thoroughly.
أطلب من الأب أن يتحقق جيدًا.
What reward do you seek?
ما هي المكافأة التي تسعى إليها؟
Mengyan seeks no reward.
منجيان لا يسعى للحصول على مكافأة.
This is a daughter-in-law's duty.
هذا واجب الكنة.
But since the matter is now clear,
ولكن بما أن الأمر أصبح واضحا الآن،
I beg Father to restore innocence
أتوسل إلى الأب أن يعيد البراءة
and release Huan Xi.
وإطلاق سراح هوان شي.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
The girl had little fortune.
كانت حظوظ الفتاة قليلة.
She took ill this morning.
لقد مرضت هذا الصباح.
And died.
ومات.
(Steadfast and Upright)
(ثابت ومستقيم)
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Huan Xi was in good health.
كان هوان شي يتمتع بصحة جيدة.
Absolutely impossible.
مستحيل تماما.
It was you.
لقد كنت أنت.
What did you do to Huan Xi?
ماذا فعلت لهوان شي؟
By house rules,
حسب قواعد المنزل،
those who fall ill must be burned and erased.
أولئك الذين يمرضون يجب حرقهم ومسحهم.
I acted for the sake of the Liu family.
لقد تصرفت من أجل عائلة ليو.
Mengyan,
منجيان،
you have no objections, do you?
ليس لديك اعتراضات، أليس كذلك؟
Huan Xi.
هوان شي.
(Steadfast and Upright)
(ثابت ومستقيم)
Do not go in.
لا تدخل.
Watch her closely.
راقبها عن كثب.
Huan Xi.
هوان شي.
(Steadfast and Upright)
(ثابت ومستقيم)
Brother-in-law.
شقيق الزوج.
Master.
يتقن.
I am guilty beyond words.
أنا مذنب إلى حد لا يمكن وصفه بالكلمات.
I failed your trust.
لقد خذلت ثقتك.
I acted out of blood ties.
لقد تصرفت بناء على روابط الدم.
In a moment of folly,
في لحظة من الحماقة،
I shielded Yaozu.
لقد قمت بحماية ياوزو.
I nearly,
انا تقريبا،
I nearly caused great harm to the Liu family.
لقد كاد أن يسبب ضررًا كبيرًا لعائلة ليو.
Wretch.
البائس.
Lift your head.
ارفع رأسك.
How did the Xie family produce such an ungrateful wolf?
كيف أنتجت عائلة شيه مثل هذا الذئب الجاحد؟
You dared steal silver from the Liu family's accounts.
لقد تجرأت على سرقة الفضة من حسابات عائلة ليو.
Brother-in-law.
شقيق الزوج.
Brother-in-law, I know I was wrong.
صهرى، أعلم أننى كنت مخطئا.
Brother-in-law, please show mercy.
يا أخي، من فضلك أظهر الرحمة.
I truly know I was wrong.
أنا أعلم حقًا أنني كنت مخطئًا.
I will never dare again, Brother-in-law.
لن أجرؤ على ذلك مرة أخرى، يا أخي.
Lock this beast in the woodshed.
أغلق هذا الوحش في مستودع الحطب.
Count everything to the last coin.
عد كل شيء حتى آخر عملة.
For every tael he stole,
لكل تايل سرقه،
cut off one of his fingers.
قطع أحد أصابعه.
Yes.
نعم.
Men.
الرجال.
Sister.
أخت.
Brother-in-law.
شقيق الزوج.
- I truly know I was wrong. - Take him away.
- أنا أعلم حقًا أنني كنت مخطئًا. - خذه بعيدًا.
Brother-in-law.
شقيق الزوج.
I beg you, Brother-in-law.
أرجوك يا أخي.
Sister.
أخت.
Please save me.
من فضلك أنقذني.
Save me, Sister.
أنقذيني يا أختي.
(Steadfast and Upright) Sister.
(ثابتة ومستقيمة) أختي.
Save me.
أنقذني.
Save me, Sister.
أنقذيني يا أختي.
Since you offered to atone,
وبما أنك عرضت التكفير،
you will be confined to the manor for three days.
سيتم حجزك في القصر لمدة ثلاثة أيام.
During these three days,
خلال هذه الأيام الثلاثة،
you will repay every coin that wretch stole from the Liu family.
سوف تعيد كل قطعة نقود سرقها هذا الوغد من عائلة ليو.
All of it without exception.
كل ذلك بلا استثناء.
For now,
في الوقت الراهن،
the household authority will temporarily be managed by Lan Mengyan.
سيتم إدارة السلطة المنزلية مؤقتًا بواسطة Lan Mengyan.
Very well.
جيد جدا.
Xie Zhaodi.
شي تشاودي.
Back then, Wanqing
في ذلك الوقت، وانكينج
gave you a name meant to bring good fortune.
لقد أعطيتك اسمًا من المفترض أن يجلب الحظ السعيد.
What a pity.
يا للأسف.
A name can be changed,
يمكن تغيير الاسم،
but fate cannot.
ولكن القدر لا يستطيع ذلك.
Your whole life,
حياتك كلها
(Steadfast and Upright.) you are destined to be dragged down by that worthless brother of yours.
(ثابت ومستقيم) أنت مقدر لك أن تسحب إلى أسفل بواسطة أخوك الذي لا قيمة له.
Settle the matters of the Xie family properly.
تسوية أمور عائلة شيه بشكل صحيح.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
your position as the Liu family's matriarch
منصبك كأم لعائلة ليو
will end here.
سوف تنتهي هنا.
Master.
يتقن.
Huan Xi.
هوان شي.
Huan Xi, look at me.
هوان شي، انظر إلي.
My lord was away just now.
لقد كان سيدي بعيدا للتو.
He could not stop this.
لم يستطع إيقاف هذا.
Please accept our condolences, Young Madam Lan.
يرجى قبول تعازينا، السيدة الشابة لان.
Wushi Powder.
مسحوق ووشي.
Qing.
تشينغ.
Liu Wenyu.
ليو وينيو.
It was Liu Wenyu.
لقد كان ليو وين يو.
That is the real reason why Xie Ruilan lied
هذا هو السبب الحقيقي وراء كذب شي رويلان
that she had the plague
أنها مصابة بالطاعون
and rushed to burn her to ashes.
وسارعوا إلى حرقها حتى تحولت إلى رماد.
Xie Ruilan.
شيه رويلان.
Old hatred and new debts,
الكراهية القديمة والديون الجديدة
we will settle them together.
سوف نستقر بهم معًا.
Sister.
أخت.
Can I leave now?
هل يمكنني المغادرة الآن؟
All those things I said,
كل تلك الأشياء التي قلتها،
that wretched woman forced me.
لقد أجبرتني تلك المرأة البائسة.
Sister, believe me.
أختي صدقيني.
Once I get out,
بمجرد خروجي،
I will tear her to pieces.
سأمزقها إلى قطع.
I will avenge you.
سأنتقم لك.
Sister.
أخت.
Move.
يتحرك.
After all the trouble you caused,
بعد كل المشاكل التي سببتها،
you still want to leave?
هل لازلت تريد المغادرة؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Blame yourself for being reckless,
لوم نفسك لكونك متهورًا،
you let Lan Mengyan catch your weakness,
لقد سمحت لـ Lan Mengyan أن يلتقط نقطة ضعفك،
and she exposed your filthy accounts.
وكشفت عن حساباتك القذرة.
How am I supposed to protect you?
كيف من المفترض أن أحميك؟
Xie Zhaodi, nonsense.
شيه Zhaodi، هراء.
I worked myself to the bone,
لقد عملت بنفسي حتى العظم،
doing all your dirty work for years.
القيام بكل أعمالك القذرة لسنوات.
If I had not abducted those girls back then,
لو لم أخطف هؤلاء الفتيات في ذلك الوقت،
what would you have used to trade for the plaque of chastity?
ما الذي كنت ستستخدمه لتتاجر به مقابل لوحة العفة؟
How else would you have gained your wealth and glory today?
فكيف كنت ستحصل على ثروتك ومجدك اليوم؟
Say something.
قل شيئا.
Say it.
قلها.
Xie Zhaodi.
شي تشاودي.
You forget
لقد نسيت
you swore before our parents
لقد أقسمت أمام والدينا
that you would protect me,
أنك تريد حمايتي،
that you would keep me safe all my life.
أنك ستحافظ على سلامتي طوال حياتي.
You forget?
هل نسيت؟
You…
أنت…
You poisoned me.
لقد سممتني.
Xie… Xie Zhaodi.
شيه ... شيه تشاودي.
You dare cut off the Xie family's bloodline?
هل تجرؤ على قطع سلالة عائلة شيه؟
How dare you face our ancestors?
كيف تجرؤ على مواجهة أسلافنا؟